[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99D_Yonas_A",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_12||(99_MSQ_35\u0026\u0026!99_MSQ_56)",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Through the Gates of Great Cleave",
        "Description": "Recover supplies being shipped through the blockade and rescue the Wardens who accompanied the delivery.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I can understand that.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "There is an old outpost in the foothills to the Northeast, and Yonas resolved that he and a handful of Wardens would push through enemy lines and capture it.\\n\\nI suggested that task be left to you, but he refused to wait.",
        "InProgressResponse": "We must recover those supplies for the outpost.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "When I saw Galahad coming up the road with those supplies, I couldn't believe it! And now the rescue of our captured Wardens as well. \\n\\nThe outpost needed supplies and reinforcements and now we have both!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99D_Galahad_C",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Secrets in the Ruins",
        "Description": "Visit the Ancient Ruins to find out what the Corrupted have been after.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Whatever it is, it can't be good.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "My thoughts exactly, and that is why I deemed the capture of this outpost to be of critical importance.\\n\\nSecuring this location has been priority, however. We haven't been able to investigate the Commander's new efforts.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If this Commander gets his hands on some Ancient source of power, all could be lost.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Your arrival is well-timed. Our scouts have just returned with excellent news - the forces of the Corrupted are vulnerable as they've spread out.\\n\\nDid you manage to discover what strategy this Commander pursues?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99D_Yonas_B",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Assessing the Enemy",
        "Description": "Join Yonas at one of the forts, get past its defenses, and discover how the Corrupted plan on contacting the source of Corruption.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"They're clearly constructing something.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, and the sooner we can dismantle their efforts, the better. \\n\\nThere is only one fortification protecting their work in the canyon. It is formidable, but it cannot be avoided.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Ironically, though we have far fewer soldiers than we had during the Wars of Crimson Madness, I believe we may yet have a chance of victory in all this.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You charged into the fort and against a small army, and now you return unscathed. That alone is quite a feat.\\n\\nBut what of your former Captain, this Commander Thorpe, was he there? Did you confront him?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99D_Yonas_C",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Sabotage the Supply Chain",
        "Description": "Assault the mines to cripple Thorpe's mining operation.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"There's not enough time. I'll do it.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Bah! You're as bull-headed now as the day I met you, but my strength is renewed now and I will not stand idly by.\\n\\nOne of us should attempt to track where the ore carts are going, while the other disables the mine.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I suspect these portals they're building may be on the high peaks to the west. We will see.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I heard the fire of cannons and hoped that had been something you did, rather than something aimed at you. \\n\\nSince you are standing before me, I'm guessing the mission was a success? That's at least one piece of good news.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99D_Galahad_E",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "All Part of the Plan",
        "Description": "Fight your way across the bridge, meet with Yash, and disable the forts on your way to the western outpost.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We need to get across the bridge.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, I am prepared to make the assault whenever you are, but speak to Galahad first and at least hear out the bright knight's plan.\\n\\nThough I wish he had conferred with us first, I admit that his reasoning is sound.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If we are to have any hope of stopping the Corrupted, we need to take back control of the bridge.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "This outpost is beyond the scope of what we planned, but I believe it will yield great value in our longer campaign against the Corrupted.\\n\\nIf your attacks on the nearby forts were successful, I believe we are secure here.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99D_Yonas_D",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Mounting An Attack",
        "Description": "Follow the route of the ore through the mountain road and destroy any unfinished portals.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Where is Yash now?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "He's gone off with Yonas, and you should follow with haste. The ore trail leads up into the Ancient ruins on the western peaks.\\n\\nIt's clear that this Commander Thorpe is constructing his evil portals up there.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I'll remain here and ensure this location is secure and you and your Wardens are not attacked from behind.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Blast it all! I am sorry, young one. I hoped to share some of the burden that has been so unevenly put on you.\\n\\nGalahad urged patience, and he was right. I fear I've led our fellow Wardens into danger once again.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99D_Yonas_F",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Beyond the Gates",
        "Description": "Rescue the captured Soulwardens, push on to the top of the mountain, confront Thorpe, and close the portal to Corruption.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Then we will rescue them once again.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, but Warden Yash places too much faith in me, I fear. He escaped as well and ranges ahead to assess the enemy position.\\n\\nSo charge on, rescue those captured, find Yash, and lets get to the peak. I'll be right behind you.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Together we are stronger than anything Corruption sends our way.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Heh, I can't believe I doubted you for even a second… but that portal, I shudder to think of what you may have witnessed in there.\\n\\nThere is no time to hear your account, however. Commander Thorpe is calling for reinforcements.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99D_Yash_F",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "To Stand Against The Dark",
        "Description": "Talk to Yonas about the plan of battle, then track down and fight Commander Thorpe.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"There must be another way.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I will NOT tolerate your bull-headed arguments this time! I'm ordering you to go south and attack Thorpe's camp before reinforcements arrive.\\n\\nWe've all agreed on this course, and we are ready to make our stand.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If our Order is to survive this war, we must defeat Commander Thorpe.\\n\\nWe'll keep the reinforcements out, but the hard fight is on you.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You defeated the bastard, didn't you? Then it was worth it.\\n\\nWe held back the reinforcements for an eternity. When all seemed lost, Yonas fought like no one else I've ever seen. He wasn't a hero, he was a legend.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99D_Grace",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Wounds Run Deep",
        "Description": "Return to the outpost and find supplies to heal Yonas. Meet up with Grace and get word from Caer Dun.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Is he alright? Can he be healed?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Well, he's in no danger of dying, but his mind is what I fear for. \\n\\nCome, let us return to the outpost and find out what medicines are available. Hopefully, our efforts restoring the supply lines have not been undone.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I still cannot believe we made it through that. I've never seen so many Corrupted in one place.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well now, there's no need to shower me with gratitude and gold, I'm just doing my part for the Soulwardens.\\n\\nI trust the medicines I brought are good enough to do the job?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Sun_p1",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99D_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "A Better Defense",
        "Description": "Shore up the defenses of Caer Dun to protect against future attacks.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What kind of ideas?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Well, Morgaine came into the command tent, saying something about using the Angry Earth blight in Edengrove to fight Corruption.\\n\\nHerbalist Sun didn't appreciate the notion so much, and they went at it.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Now that I'm here, it would be shame not to at least duck my head into some of these ruins.\\n\\nI had a bad streak in Weaver's Fen, but my luck's turning around... I can feel it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "There you are! We need to go to Edengrove, you and I. \\n\\nYour sorceress friend, Morgaine, has concocted a very dangerous plan, and I need your help talking her out of it.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
